INFO:



Dmytro HoiPython Developer

E-mail: me@dmytrohoi.com
LinkedIn: dmytrohoi
Telegram: @dmytrohoi
Site: dmytrohoi.com

SUMMARY:

I have been programming in Python for over two years. I worked on the following projects: the custom test framework on Python for medical project(real medical device); sites parsing scripts on Python/JS/SQL with Regex; Telegram bots for parsing sites, for connecting to the server via the REST API and for creating reminders; small personal projects on Django and Flask; script for faster creation and deployment of a personal site; contribution to some projects on GitHub. [more on dmytrohoi.com/blog/projects]

My additional programming languages is: Go, Javascript, sh, Ruby. I finished studying Systems Analysis, including machine learning.

I have the basic skills of a programming engineer: knowing HTTP/HTML/CSS, SQL, Regex, Bash/zsh, Git (a specific tools: Gerrit, git-flow, TortoiseSVN).

I understand: the principles of OOP/SOLID/DRY, REST API, basic design patterns in QA/SE and several BA tools (Jira, Jama).

SKILLS:

- Languages: Python, Go, JavaScript, Ruby, sh, Pascal/Delphi*
- Libraries/Frameworks: pytest, Django, Flask, appium, SQLAlchemy, requests, bs4, tkinter, Jupyter, Pelican
- IDE/Code Editors: VSCode**, VIM
- English-level: Intermediate
- OS: Ubuntu, Arch, Windows
- Tools: Git, SVN, Jira, Jama, Slack/MS Teams, pip, venv/pipenv
- Other: HTML/CSS, SQL, Regex**, GitHub**, sr.ht, Docker

^{* -} in progress, small experience or was used once-twice in projects

^{** -} used every day and gaining experience

ADDITIONALS SKILLS:

- Algorithmic & Design thinking
- Initiative and pro-active
- Public speaking skill
- Process automation loving
- Writing articles (habr.com/users/dmytrohoi | dev.to/dmytrohoi | higaindev.ml)
- Adobe Photoshop, MSOffice, Draw.io and else basics
- SMM, PR, Poems writing

PERSONAL PROJECTS:

- Pelican Quick Site Builder (available on PyPI)
- hi gain dev Programming Blog
- <u>Kiwi Tickets Parser</u> (with GUI) and <u>Telegram Bots</u>

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Company: GlobalLogic

Position: Python Developer in Test / AQA (05/2019 - now)

Info: Implementation of the custom test framework for the embedded device on Android

Pie (using Python, Appium, ADB, and pytest)

Company: Microbilt

Position: Site Scraping Script Developer (07/2018 - 05/2019)

Info: programming with Regex and SQL, Python and Javascript automation scripting

Company: National University of Radioelectronics

Position: Senior Assistant (06/2016 - 05/2017)

Info: Quality Assurance Department ISO 9001 using for internal quality assurance system

EDUCATION:



<u>Kharkiv National University of</u> <u>Radioelectronics</u>

- Bachelor (2014 2018) Electronics - "Electronics devices and systems"
- Master (2018 2019)
 System Analysis "Consolidated information"

DMYTRO HOI / Feb 2020 2/2

E-mail: me@dmytrohoi.com | LinkedIn: dmytrohoi | Site: dmytrohoi.com | Site: <a href="megdmytrohoi